<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Versions>
  <Version Number="1.0.0" Name="">
    <Features>
      <Feature>Daily timer management.</Feature>
      <Feature>Manual Timer Adjustment.</Feature>
      <Feature>Export Direct To Jira.</Feature>
      <Feature>Jira issue search (with saved filters).</Feature>
      <Feature>Alerts when no timer is running.</Feature>
      <Feature>Machine locked time capture.</Feature>
      <Feature>Automatic Updates.</Feature>
      <Feature>Export Stats &amp; A Target Export Amount.</Feature>
    </Features>
    <Bugs />
    <Others />
  </Version>
  <Version Number="1.0.1" Name="">
    <Features>
      <Feature>Intergrated updates in spotify style.</Feature>
      <Feature>Nice error reporting back to central store.</Feature>
    </Features>
    <Bugs />
    <Others />
  </Version>
  <Version Number="1.0.2" Name="">
    <Features />
    <Bugs>
      <Bug>Critical export bug fix.</Bug>
    </Bugs>
    <Others />
  </Version>
  <Version Number="1.0.3" Name="">
    <Features>
      <Feature>Added viewable change log.</Feature>
      <Feature>Locked timers show recent timers, rather than todays timers (auto create if not already created).</Feature>
      <Feature>Jira Cache, all queries returning issues from Jira are cached for 14 days and used to populate drop-down on add/rename timers.</Feature>
      <Feature>Added tray icon pop-out when update avaliable.</Feature>
    </Features>
    <Bugs>
      <Bug>Simplified export window.</Bug>
      <Bug>Changed icons for Manual Adjust &amp; Rename.</Bug>
      <Bug>Better handling of timers left running overnight.</Bug>
    </Bugs>
    <Others />
  </Version>
  <Version Number="1.0.4" Name="">
    <Features>
      <Feature>Add ability to set working days &amp; start of week for target calculations.</Feature>
      <Feature>Add ToolTips to all windows to help users.</Feature>
      <Feature>Add keyboard shortcut to export an entire day of un-exported timers.</Feature>
      <Feature>Added drag &amp; drop from Jira to app to create timer/start timer if already present.</Feature>
      <Feature>Change the timer adjustment to an up and down arrow rather than radio buttons.</Feature>
    </Features>
    <Bugs>
      <Bug>Corrected bug with export target on Sundays being zero, but exported being correct.</Bug>
      <Bug>Adding locked timer invalid check of timer presence for adding to existing.</Bug>
      <Bug>Corrected some windows being top most &amp; hiding pop-ups.</Bug>
      <Bug>Only show build reference on Beta builds, all others are always "0" so pointless.</Bug>
      <Bug>Change ordering of Jiras to use new comparer to sort numerical parts correctly.</Bug>
      <Bug>Prevent flashing of UI when refreshing.</Bug>
      <Bug>Remove Stopwatch in locked timer to make display more accurate. Do not need regualar update, machine is locked.</Bug>
    </Bugs>
    <Others />
  </Version>
  <Version Number="1.1.0" Name="">
    <Features>
      <Feature>Drag &amp; Drop can change the tab</Feature>
      <Feature>Clicking update avaliable baloon will restart the app and install the update.</Feature>
      <Feature>Added auto update, when new update installed, the app automatically restarts to use new version.</Feature>
      <Feature>Added default export remaining time value.</Feature>
      <Feature>Added option to set the comment prefix, default same as previous "Gallifrey".</Feature>
      <Feature>Included Remote Desktop connect/disconnect to session switch for better lock/unlock detection</Feature>
    </Features>
    <Bugs>
      <Bug>Added error handling for condition when selected timer disappears (normally on app open/close).</Bug>
      <Bug>Better handling of deleting locked timers and which items selected after delete.</Bug>
      <Bug>Reduce drag and drop area to tab list as this makes more sense.</Bug>
      <Bug>Correct issue with page title not being updated once a new timer is added.</Bug>
      <Bug>Changed check/install updates to single click to by-pass .net issue with copying label text on double click.</Bug>
      <Bug>Changing timer date now maintains exported &amp; current time values.</Bug>
      <Bug>Fixed issue when unable to locate Jira when exporting (due to Jira rename)</Bug>
    </Bugs>
    <Others />
  </Version>
  <Version Number="1.1.1" Name="">
    <Features>
      <Feature>Drag &amp; Drop feature no defaults to "start now".</Feature>
      <Feature>Added Optional Export Prompts With Ability To Select Just Changed Time, Or All Exported Time.</Feature>
    </Features>
    <Bugs>
      <Bug>Fixed change log to show only the latest version.</Bug>
      <Bug>When editing timer and nothing changed, the OK button closes the form.</Bug>
      <Bug>Handling error when adding locked timer to selected item.</Bug>
      <Bug>Adding locked time to new timer adds to correct day.</Bug>
    </Bugs>
    <Others />
  </Version>
  <Version Number="1.1.2" Name="">
    <Features>
      <Feature>Change Jira interaction to use hand rolled REST API communication layer to open more features.</Feature>
      <Feature>Add display of parent issue when Jira is a sub-task.</Feature>
      <Feature>Show remaining estimate in the export window.</Feature>
      <Feature>Assign to current user when adding new timer.</Feature>
      <Feature>Set in-progress when adding new timer.</Feature>
    </Features>
    <Bugs>
      <Bug>Fixed issue with drag and drop with custom Jira URLs.</Bug>
      <Bug>Issue when drag and drop with no timers on current date, start now not checked.</Bug>
      <Bug>Fixed issue where you can subtract more time than you had already exported from a timer.</Bug>
      <Bug>Fixed issue where unexported time will subtract values from timers with a negative unexported time.</Bug>
      <Bug>Fixed issue with locked timers when deleting time and leaving just one, it's not selected by default.</Bug>
      <Bug>Fixed issue on locked timer window when trying to export with no timers selected.</Bug>
      <Bug>Make export date non changable non the export screen.</Bug>
      <Bug>Better handling of errors when trying to get updates.</Bug>
    </Bugs>
    <Others />
  </Version>
</Versions>
